hi I'm Bonita Roy I'm the founding
associate for app associates
international and I hope you will enjoy
this video version of our spring
newsletter now the purpose of this video
is first of all to thank you for your
interest in support network but also to
update you on what's been happening and
what we might be doing in the future but
I also want to extend to you an
invitation to participate in a broader
and deeper way to engage some of the
offerings that we have on website app
associates net to take a really good
look at our workshops and retreats and
the different events that we offer and
to consider taking some of the courses
especially the courses that make up the
certification track
now out an app associates means applying
participatory practices and
organizations and the workplace and our
applications are heuristics models
templates tools and techniques to move
from the old obsolete structures and the
old ways of thinking inside the dominant
discourse or an old paradigm and shift
them to more open broadly democratic and
more participatory ways of
organizational life our larger goal is
to support organizational innovation
social innovation of all kinds in many
different venues around the world so
we're interested in building a critical
threshold a group of professionals who
have a very very robust intellectual and
grounded in practically sound
understanding of the challenges that
organizations face the history of the
modern organization what we've done in
the past what are the conditions have
created the kinds of obstacles we face
today and then take that and be able to
work that into very very radically
provocative and disruptive in innovative
ways of looking at organizational life
so that's the invitation I hope that it
piques your interest I hope you have
enthusiasm for it I hope you can join us
and in a and a broader participation
when you visit our website look around
and find the certification track and you
will see that we are offering a three
day workshop in a retreat center in a
very beautiful setting near here in
Litchfield it'll be the first course the
foundational course that is a broad
overview
the principles the practices and the
processes of open participation of this
new participatory zeitgeist it's already
making its way already making changes in
our organizations so please check that
out and I hope you can join us and
finally I wanted to share an update on
what I call my European to learn that
occurred last month and I want to thank
the individuals and the organizations
that made that possible I had the
opportunity to work with the european
centre of leadership practice in harlem
netherlands i worked with the sensor for
transformative leadership and Tom time
norway and i was really happy to do the
three-day retreat at the house of sh
marble which is in beautiful farmland in
germany just outside the German Polish
border and that was hosted by Uncas body
and Johan ends von Essen so we received
a great deal of encouragement and really
enthusiastic feedback about that
workshop and it has become the
foundational course for a certification
track we also were invited to
participate in Berlin change days in
october to do a workshop on disruptive
change that we're calling it how the
impossible and improbable becomes the
obvious and edible and so we're going to
do it two day workshop at the beginning
of the Berlin change days in october and
hopefully we'll be doing an advanced
course again at the house of smart girl
shortly after that so those are some of
the things
in the work and finally I also have the
opportunity to experience the synergy
hub in Rotterdam and engage with social
innovation labs that are working there
the communities around United Earth
neural map and unity so I wanted to give
a shout out to young and Curtis and
Robert and Andrea and Brett and thank
them for their support and thank them
for really diving into some provocative
explorations and some deep conversations
so that's about it thank you for
watching and if you know someone who
might be interested on work please share